https://www.carmel.ac.uk/policies-procedures/privacy-notice/

Applying
Why Choose Carmel College?
BTEC Information Technology
BTEC Performing Arts (Theatre)
Student Success
Why Choose Us and the University of Liverpool?
Liverpool Hope University Accommodation
Why Choose Us and the Liverpool Hope University?
Carmel University Centre Facilities
Prep for Degree Study : FREE 6 Week Evening Course!
Data Protection Officer: Charles Burton, Assistant Principal, Carmel College
The College collects and processes personal data of students to enable us to provide Further and Higher Educational courses. Carmel College is committed to being transparent about how it collects and uses that data and to meeting its data protection obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation. This Privacy Notice relates to our processing of personal data of past, present and prospective students.
Carmel Privacy Notice 07-01-20
Policies and Procedures
Eduroam
Other College Policies
The Local Offer
Safeguarding
Equality and Diversity
Attendance and Absence
Health and Safety
Privacy Notice
Downloads
From this page you can download our Prospectus, Course Leaflets, and other useful information.
“
Carmel has enabled me to gain many skills as well as important experiences and my time here has been something I will never forget. My lessons have challenged me and taken me out of my comfort zone, something I am very thankful for.
”
Jocelyn Mathew - Studying BTEC Applied Science, Law, Health & Social Care
“
Being at Carmel has made me more ambitious and excited for my future career. I have learnt never to give up and to always work hard to achieve my goals. Carmel has been an amazing experience and one I’ll never forget.
”
Jess Maudsley - Studying BTEC Science, BTEC Health & Social Care (Double)
“
I have really enjoyed my time at Carmel as there's lots to get involved in. I'm hoping to do a degree in IT when I leave and the teaching and support I've had has prepared me to embrace the challenges of the real world.
”
Thomas Samuel - Studying BTEC IT (Double), BTEC Science
“
I have really enjoyed studying at Carmel. It’s enabled me to make friends for life and develop skills for the future. I have become much more independent but have also been supported in order to achieve my best.
”
Isabel Hamand - Studying Economics, Mathematics, Psychology
“
Carmel has helped me become the person I am today. I’m really grateful to my tutors for helping me become more independent and able to push myself further to achieve my goals. I've also met some great friends and had some moments which I'll never forget!
”
Rio Gill - Studying Business Studies, History, Physical Education
“
The opportunities I've accessed at Carmel have allowed me to discover what I'm passionate about. I'm happy with the support I've had from my tutors and I've found the challenge of my subjects satisfying. I believe I will succeed in the future.
”
Ray Sheridan-Warburton - Studying Biology, Chemistry, English Literature, Maths
“
At Carmel I have enjoyed meeting new people and I’ve become more responsible and independent. The teachers and support staff are very helpful and I’ve also had lots of opportunities to develop new skills.
”
Alex Hackett - Studying Foundation Learning Entry Level
HighAchievers
FutureProfessionals
OpenEvents
CampusMap
News & Events
Former Art Foundation student appears in Vogue Magazine
Starting university this year has been a unique experience for all students. They have had to adapt to a completely different way of learning and…
Read More »
Student wins BAE Systems Tempest Comp
Congratulations to Lower Sixth student, Cameron Poulter, who recently won the BAE Systems ‘Tempest’ competition. BAE Systems is the UK’s largest defence company. It is…
Read More »
Student to share faith around the world
Congratulations to Upper Sixth student, Daniel Canning, who has just secured a place to become a missionary in Australia next October! Daniel studies Maths, Physics…
Read More »
All News & Events
Tweets by CarmelCollege
Downloads
From this page you can download our Prospectus, Course Leaflets, and other useful information.
Facilities Hire
Need facilities for your club, business meeting or event with free car parking on site?
